timeanywhere.com 2015-10-29

# NOVAtime - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

NOVAtime respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us, including your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address, will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of NOVAtime or authorized NOVAtime partners and resellers. NOVAtime, or one of our authorized partners or resellers, may contact you in regards to NOVAtime products or related services. 

## Collected Information:

We require customers who register to use the services offered on our Site (collectively, the "Service") to give us contact information, such as their name, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. At the time you express interest in attaining additional information, or when you register for the Service, we may also ask for additional personal information, such as title, mobile number, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees, industry or decision timeframe. Customers can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked.

NOVAtime uses the information that we collect to set up the Service for individuals and their organizations. NOVAtime, or one of our authorized partners or resellers may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our Products and the Service that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customers are invited to receive an email newsletter. Customer email addresses and any personal customer information will not be distributed or shared with third parties. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to [sales@novatime.net.](mailto:sales@novatime.net)

## Third-Party Sites:

The Site contains links to other web sites. NOVAtime is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. NOVAtime is making third party links available for reference purposes only and assumes no responsibility for any information contained therein or for any services provided by the individuals, firms, or organizations referenced. Additionally, these linked websites, their organizations, and their services are not reviewed, controlled, examined, sponsored, or endorsed by NOVAtime. Furthermore, NOVAtime does not warrant or guarantee that the third party websites will be free of infection by viruses, worms, or any other destructive agents. In no event shall NOVAtime be liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss arising from or occasioned by the use of these websites or the information they contain. NOVAtime is providing these linked sites to you only as a convenience, and it is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential. NOVAtime cautions you to make sure that you completely understand the potential risks before accessing linked sites through the NOVAtime website (including the potential infection of your system by computer viruses). 

## Opt-Out Policy:

NOVAtime uses the information that we collect to set up the Service for individuals and their organizations. NOVAtime, or one of our authorized partners or resellers may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our Products and the Service that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customers are invited to receive an email newsletter. Customer email addresses and any personal customer information will not be distributed or shared with third parties. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to [sales@novatime.net.](mailto:sales@novatime.net)

## Rights to Modify:

NOVAtime reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should email to [sales@novatime.net.](mailto:sales@novatime.net)
